Guide to the Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
- Series VI. Genealogy Research and Allied Families
  - VI-A. Robert Croll Stevens Research Files
    - Knauss, Howard C., 1948-1988 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Knauss, John W., 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Knauss, Leonard, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Knauss, Lloyd, 1934-1987 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Knauss, Manfred, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Knauss, Peter, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Knauss, Stephen C., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Knauss, Stuart, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Knauss, Ulrike, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Knauss, Walter Jr., 1955-1990 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Knauss, William D., 1954-1990 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Knight, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Knowles, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Knowles (oversized chart), n.d. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Knowlton, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Lamb, n.d., 1960, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Langstaff, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Leach, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Henry, 1974-1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Ralph William III, 1957-1990 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Lewis, 1907, 1986-1991 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Lindsay, 1949-1983 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Linnell, 1983-1990 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Linnell, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Linnell - Boston Transcript columns, 1901-1928 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Linnell Family Association, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Lovett/Tantum/Bacon, 1978-1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Lufkin, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Lumbar/Lombard/Lumbert, 1848-1883 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Lumpkin, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - McMorrow, Frances Townley (May), 1979-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - McNeill, Sally, 1975-1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Mace, Mrs. H. Lansing (Reumann), 1978-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Mansfield, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Marsh, 1887, 1893 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Marsters/Masters, 1958, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Martin, James, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Martin, John, 1931 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Martin, Louise Pond, 1924-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Martin, Robert S., 1925-1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Martinez-Cardeza, 1975-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Martinez-Cardeza, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Martinez-Cardeza, 1984-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Martinez-Cardeza: Exhibits 1-11, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Mather, 1890, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Mayo, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Meffert, Sallie, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Merrick, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Moulton, 1906 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Newbury, Janet Ruth (Binetsch), 1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Nichols, Jeffrey Paul, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Nichols, Marion Fay Reuman, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Nickse, Kenneth L., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Nickse, Louise, 1979-1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Nickse, Tom, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Nickse, Wallace C. R., 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Packard, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Page, 1893 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Parmelee, Patrick, 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Parmelee, Perry, 1984-1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Parsons, 1972, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Partridge, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Peasley, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Penney, 1897, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Perkins, 1959, 1988, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Pfeifer, Traudel, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Phillips, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Phinney, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Pinder (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Pond, 1975-1991 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
    - Pond - "The Pond History" by James D. Pond, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
    - Pond, Elizabeth, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Pond, Freeman C., 1896-1992, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Pond, Mrs. James D., 1905-1989 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Pond, Lindsay, 1907-1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Pond, Robert L., 1977-1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Poynter, Marion K., 1970-1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Prence, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Proctor, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Proctor, 1981-1987 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Reed, Dorothea Stevens, 1953-1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Remington, Natalie May (Stevens), 1979-1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Reuman, Evelyn S. (Mrs. Arthur), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Reuman, Frieda, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Reumann, Otto: Memoirs, 1961, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Reuman, Mrs. Otto G., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Reuman, Paul B., 1984-1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Reuman, Peter D., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Reuman, Robert E., 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Reuman, Steven R., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Reuman, Warren, and Mrs. Theodore Reuman, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Reumann, Christian, 1977-1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Reumann, Rev. John, 1984-1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Reyner, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Rider, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Ridgway, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Ring/Deane, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Roberts, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Rogers, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Rolfe, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Rosenblum, Kathryn and Carl, 1956-1991 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Sanders, 1912-1922, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Scruggs, Joyce Nichols, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Shattuck, Ann Howe Stevens, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Shelley, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Shephard, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Shreve/Sheriff, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Silver, 1853-1911, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Simpson, Nancy, 1976- Aug. 1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Simpson, Nancy, Sept. 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Sligar, Barbara (Pond), 1965-1990 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Smith, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Smith, 1982-1990 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Burley & Augustus, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Richard, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Snow, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Snow, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Snyder - Correspondence, 1975-1990 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Sommer, Gerd C., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Sparrow (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Speer, 1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
    - Spencer, Dickson H., 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Sproule, 1856-1980 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Sproule, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Sproule, 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Stevens: Miscellaneous, 1858-1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Stevens, Albert Gallatin & Sarah Caroline Greene Stevens, 1977, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Stevens, Edward Webster Dann, 1954-1983 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Stevens, Frederick C. (1856-1916), 1974-1979, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Stevens, Frederick C. Jr. (1890-1965), 1890-1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Stevens, Frederick C. III (Ted), 1978-1982 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Stevens, Frederick Plummer, 1866, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Stevens, Isabelle C., n.d. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Stevens, Jane Alden, 1969, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Stevens, Jean Virginia, 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Stevens, Pauline Croll, 1975-1982 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Stevens, Richard Stonington, 1979-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Stevens, Robert Hastings (1802-1889), 1975-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Stevens, Robert Hastings (b. 1907), 1950-Mar. 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Stevens, Robert Hastings (b. 1907), April 1976-1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Stevens, Samuel C., 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Susan Cora, 1980-1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Stevens, William, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, William Croll, 1981-1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Stockinger, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Stockton, 1977-1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Stokes, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Stoothoff, Marjorie Beck (Bahret), 1984-1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Thaxter, 1921 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Thayer, 1938, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Thompson, David, 1913 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Thompson, John, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Tracy, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Treat, n.d., 1915 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Trumbull, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Wadleigh, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Walton, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Warren, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Weeks, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Weigers, Peg, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Welding, Jane Knauss, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Wheeler, David, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Whelden, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Whittier, 1873, 1937, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Wilcoxson, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Williams, 1915, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Willis, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Windmüller, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Winslow (see Chilton), n.d., 1985 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Wise, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Witham, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Withington, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Wollmeäser, Friedrich R., 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Woolman, 1977-1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Wynn, Rachel L., 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Young, John, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Young - Correspondence, 1976-1990 (Box 18, Folder 13+)
    - Zimmerman, Anne Louise (Martin), 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Zimmerman, Carol, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Zimmerman, David, 1976-1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Appenidix A - Bahret (revised), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Appendix B - Royal Descent, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - VI-B. Robert Hastings Stevens (b. 1907) Research Files
    - Almy, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Badgley, 1951-1955 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Badgley (Dutchess Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Badgley (Long Island & NJ) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Badgley (Saratoga Co.), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Bailey, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Barnes (William) (Hastings), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Barnes (Thomas) (Olney) - Albee, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Barton, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Bellow, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Bond (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Bradley, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Brown & Murford, 1953-1954, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Burton, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Card & Graves, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Carr, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Chase, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Clark, 1950-1957, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Clark, Angeline & Kneeland (see also Kneeland), 1951, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Clark, John Whipple, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Clark, Stephen, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Clark - Newport property & local inquiry 1952, 1952, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Clough, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Cochran, Robert and Ann, 1951-1955, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Cochran, William, 1951-1958, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Coggeshall, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Colby, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Davis, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Easton, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Eaton, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Ellison, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Embree & Parcell, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Field, 1952, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Fry, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Funk, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Funk-Cochran, 1951-1955 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Gardiner, Andrew (Dr.), 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Gardiner, Uncle John, of Rio Vista, CA, 1906-1914 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Gardiner - Miscellaneous: Correspondence, 1903-1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Gardiner - Miscellaneous: Correspondence (Oversized items), 1867, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Gardiner - Miscellaneous: Notes, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Green(e), 1950-1955 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Greene (Putnam County), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Greene (Rhode Island) (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Greene, Nathan (Saratoga), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Greene, Nathan S. (Herkimer Co. & Wisconsin), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Greene, Nathan S., western branches, & Jerome, 1950-1958 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Greene, Nathan, Stephen B., Wm Augustus, & Sarah Caroline, 1943-1981, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Greene, Dr. Stephen B., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Greene-Belding, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Haight, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Harcut (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Hastings, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Hastings (Revolution), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hastings, Robert, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hawkins, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hawkins, Christopher, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Heath, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Heywood/Heyward, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Hillman, 1952-1974, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Hills, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Holman, Winifred Lovering, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Hoyt (Hastings), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Hunt, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Karr, 1951-1956 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Kent, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Kneeland & Clark (see also Clark), 1920-1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Lauderbach, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Lufkin, 1950-1951, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Marsh (Hastings), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Matthewson, 1951, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Millard, 1951, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Moore, A.C. (see also Card & Graves), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Newspaper clippings: Research in England, 1951-1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Olney, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Page, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Partridge, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Penny, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Potter, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Rodman, 1951, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Rolfe, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Rounds, Edith D. Clarke, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Rowell, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Sanders (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Saratoga (Greene & Badgley), 1951-1955 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Sayles, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Shadbolt, 1951-1952, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Stansbury, 1974, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Stevens (New England) (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Trumbull, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Weed-Wensly, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Wheeler & Wise, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Whipple, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Whipple - Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Whipple - Vermont, Mass., & migration west, 1838-1955 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Whittier, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Wicks, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Williams (Salisbury), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Roger, 1936-1953, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Xeroxed notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - VI-C. Stevens FamilyIncludes Achilles, Allen, Flood, Greene, Knight, Lee, Olney, Smith, Sproule, and Whipple Lines
    Includes Achilles, Allen, Flood, Greene, Knight, Lee, Olney, Smith, Sproule, and Whipple Lines
    - Stevens Family
      - Archelaus Stevens: Subpoena ticket, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Otho Stevens: Deed, 1764 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Birth, marriage, death records: Hamstead, NH (copies), 1752-1797 (Box OS, Folder Cons)
      - Bible records and other listings (births, marriages, deaths) (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Genealogies by Albert G. Stevens (manuscripts), 1868, 1890 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - "Genealogy of Otho Stevens", manuscript by Albert G. Stevens, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - "General Ancestry of Nancy Dunbar Stevens Baker, Jane Alden Stevens, William Croll Stevens, Ann Howe Stevens", n.d (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - "Stevens Notes Compiled for Robert Hastings Stevens, M.D.," by Winifred Lovering Holman, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 8-Jul)
      - "Excerpts From Pillsbury Ancestry" by Mary Lovering Holman, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - "Excerpts From The Old Families of Salisbury and Amesbury" by David W. Hoyt, 1897 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Research in Enosburg Falls, VT (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Flood (Floyd) Family
      - "Some Descendents of Philip Flood (Floyd) of Newbury, Massachusetts", 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Green(e) Family
      - Stephen B. Green. Medical license, 1826 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Knight Family
      - Correspondence, 1806-1828 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Financial documents, 1810-1824 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - "The Relation of Susanna Knight", 1805 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Olney-Whipple Family
      - Correspondence (photostats), 1791-1813 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Account book (photostats), 1787-1803 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Smith-Achilles-Allen Family
      - "The Search for John Smith": Reference 1-2, 4-5, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - "The Search for John Smith": Reference 3, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - "The Search for John Smith": Reference 6-8, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - "The Search for John Smith": Reference 9, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Smith Family in New Hampshire: Research, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Smith Family in New Hampshire: Research, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Smith Family: "Book of Record as Kept by Burley Smith", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Smith-Achilles Family: Financial documents and commissions, 1768-1836 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Smith-Achilles Family: Newspaper clippings, 1859, 1901, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Smith-Achilles-Allen Family: Correspondence, 1813-1855 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Lydia Lee (Knight) Smith: Birthday book, 1885 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Sproule Family
      - Andrew Sproule: Patent, 1884 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Helen Sproule: Scrapbook, 1885-1912 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - VI-D. Knauss Family
    - Dorothy Pond Knauss - Miscellaneous items, 1897, 1966, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Edwin S. Knauss and Dorothy P. Knauss estates, 1951-1975 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Knauss Bros. - Hickory Smoked Ham wrapper (Folder 1)
    - Knauss family - Hindenburg materials, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Souvenir - small Hindenburg model, 1936 (Box 71, Folder -)
    - Knauss family - Olympic scarf, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - VI-E. Croll Family
    Includes Blackburne, Knowles, and Sharpe lines
    - Croll Family
      - Albert G. Croll - Deeds (Box ??, Folder Cons)
      - Albert G. Croll - Mortgage with Eliza Arundel, 1848-1875 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Albert G. Croll - Mortgage with Eliza Arundel, 1870 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Albert G. Croll - Cemetery deed, 1886 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Albert Ivins Croll - Estate papers, 1932-1938 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Albert Ivins Croll - 1904 tript to Japan/China letters; transcription “Journey to the Pacific, the Letters of Albert Ivins Croll, Feburary 2 to May 26, 1904”, compiled by Robert C. Stevens and Ann H. Stevens, 2010; research material for transcript (Box 91, Folder 1-4)
        -Includes addendum - January 12 and 23, May 3, 1904
      - Sarah Helen (Knowles) Croll - Estate papers, 1938-1942 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Sarah Helen (Knowles) Croll - List of properties, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Sarah Helen (Knowles) Croll - Appraisals, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - Croll family - Financial documents, 1884-1908 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Croll and allied families scrapbook, 1915-1939 (Box 28, Folder -)
    - Blackburne-Sharpe Family
      - Christopher John Blackburne: Notebook, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Emily L. Blackburne: Birthday book, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Emily L. Blackburne: Bank book, 1894-1901 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Ida P. Croll Blackburne: Journal/cook book, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Ida P. Croll Blackburne: Cook book, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Ida P. Croll Blackburne: Cemetery plot deed, 1932 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - John Blackburne: High School yearbook, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - John Sharp Blackburne: Military certificates, 1925, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Blackburne Coat of arms, 1895 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence and loose envelopes, 1895-1948, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Baptism, marriage, funeral documents, 1885-1948, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Financial documents, 1859-1913, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Legal documents and estate papers, 1865-1939, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Estate papers: Ida Blackburne cemetery deed, 1932 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper clippings: Social events, weddings, obituaries, articles, poetry, recipes, 1878-1950, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Newspaper clippings: Estates and inheritance, 1915-1933, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper clippings: Real estate, 1896-1923, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous: Poetry, calling cards, flyers, lists, 1884, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Genealogy: Notes and charts (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Genealogy: Robert C. Stevens correspondence, 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Genealogy: Media Research Bureau, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Knowles Family
      - Tamzen (Linnell) Knowles - Estate papers, 1933-1945 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Series VII. Regional History: Maps and Articles
  - Other newspapers, 1940, 1954 (Folder 1)
  - VII-A. Kansas (and surrounding area)
    - Maps
      - "Sectional Map of the State of Kansas" published by G.W. & C.B. Colton & Co., 1870 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Map of Indian Territory in the Kansas area, 1879 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Map of Kansas City, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Map of Kansas Counties: Crawford, Cherokee, Labette, Neosho, Wilson, Montgomery, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Views in the city of St. Joseph, Missouri, 1887 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Map of Park Co. Colorado, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Map: Sohell Town Co. Lands (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Land Department, St. Paul & Duluth R.R. Co. (scouting land in the Mille Lac Reservation) (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Map of the city of Parsons, Kansas, 1877 (Folder 2)
    - Articles and Newspapers
      - Newspaper: The Parsons Sun: Katy Special, 23-May-70 (Box 26, Folder -)
      - Newspaper: The Parsons Sun Centennial, 29-Jul-71 (Box 26, Folder -)
      - Newspaper: Parsons Sun, May 4-5, 1991; May 16, 1991 (Box 26, Folder -)
      - Prints: "Lawrence Kansas Illustrated No.2: Lawrence and Douglas County in the National News. 1856-1890." By Glenn Kappelman (2 copies) (Box 26, Folder -)
      - "Parsons Palladium", 1895 (Folder 1)
  - VII-B. New York
    - Maps
      - New York Central Railroad, West Shore Railroad: New York Central Lines, Map of the New York Terminal District, issued by Freight Traffic Department, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Map of Middleville Quadrangle, NY, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Map of Saratoga Quadrangle, NY, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Map of Wyoming County, NY, 1916 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Map of Wyoming County, NY, 1916 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Map of Genosee County, NY, 1916 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Articles and Newspapers
      - Articles on Stevens homes and Attica, 1963-1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Newspaper: Attica Sesquicentennial, Keepsake Edition, Then & Now, 1837-1987 (Box 26, Folder -)
- Series VIII. Photographs
  - VIII-A. People
    - Aldrich family, 1903, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Bahret family, 1899-1966, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 8-10)
    - Baile, Robert Winfield, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Barrows family, 1973, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Barrows, Kate E. (Briggs) (1850-1903), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Barrows (Greenberg Whaley), Mary Stevens (b. 1975) and husbands (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Baur family, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Beck family, 1918, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Beckley family, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Binetsch family, 1888-1987, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 16-19)
    - Black, Mable (Stevens) (1867-1936), n.d. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Blackburne family, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Blackburne family, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Brown family, 1970, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Burwell, George N. and Glenny family, 1926 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Camnitz family, 1971, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Cardeza (see Martinez-Cardeza) (Box -, Folder -)